

Lynette Jane A. Bojocan

Virtual Assistant with 1+ years of experience with email marketing, customer service and data entry. Aiming to work and to be exposed in a competitive working environment, and gain more knowledge and skill that will not only enhance my capabilities but as well as be more beneficial to the company that I work with.



lynettejane0923@gmail.com

+639565942637

Work Experience

Virtual Assistant

California Based | Onlinejobs.ph May 21, 2022 to June 12, 2023

- Data Entry
- Email Marketing
- Google Docs
- Customer Service

Bookkeeper

Tubig Please Water Refilling Station | Llorente E. Samar December 2020 to May 2022

- Update Journal and Ledger transaction Records
- Monitor Inventories
- Monitor Cash Flows
- Payroll
- Filing Income Tax Return

Customer Service Representative

The Results Companies | Mactan Newtown, Lapu-lapu City March 2018 to September 2018

- Technical Service
- Answer Customer's Inquiries
- Sales

Education

Saint Paul School of Professional Studies

Bachelor of Science in Commerce

Major in Business Management | June 2011 - April 2016

Skills

Hard Skills

- QuickBooks Intuit
- Chat GPT Open AI
- Amazon FBA
- Bookkeeping
- Google Docs
- Microsoft Office Tools
- Computer Skills
- Email Management
- Data Entry
- Market Research

Soft Skills

- Self Initiative
- Adaptable
- Patience
- Crisis Management
- Relationship Building
- Costumer Oriented

Trainings and Seminars

Quick Pro | May 2022

- Excel Basic Formulas
- QuickBooks Intuit
- Amazon FBA